Capital District Regional Planning Commission; Records apap380
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Rensselaer County, 1937-2003; 3; 8.01 cubic ft.
  - [City of] Troy, Initial Housing Element, 1972 October (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - [City of] Troy, A Management Study of the Bureau of Police, Vol. 1, 1972 December (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - [City of] Troy, A Management Study of the Bureau of Police, Vol. 2, 1973 February (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Troy, Preliminary Geotechnical Engineering Study, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 March (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Troy, A Profile of the Community, 1983 December (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Troy, Proposed City Charter, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Troy, Recreation Open Space Analysis, [Draft Copy], 1973 September (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Troy, Recreation Open Space Inventory, 1973 October (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Troy, Recreation Open Space Plan, 1974 June (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Troy, Renaissance Along the Hudson and The Atrium of Troy and the Frear Building [Brochure], Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Troy, Report on Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1965 September (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Troy, Report on Traffic Factors Related to the Development the Uncle Sam Mall, 1972 June (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Troy, Residential Revitalization Loan Program, [Application], 1978 October (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Troy, Summary Feasibility Study, Oakwood Business Park, 1990 May (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Troy, Summary Report, Oakwood Avenue Traffic Study, 1990 January (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Troy, Traffic Control Device Inventory, 1974 October (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Troy, Traffic Control Device Street Location Book, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Troy, TRIP Housing, 1972 September (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Troy, Troy Area Committee on Health Access, Report on Access Barriers and Service GAPS, 1990 July (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Troy, Troy Rehabilitation and Improvement Program(TRIP), Inc. [Informational Brochure], 1984 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Troy, Two Centuries of Public Service: History of Troy Water Works, [Brochure], Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - [City of] Troy, Welcome to Troy's Water Treatment Plant [Brochure], Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - [Village of] Valley Falls, Engineer's Preliminary Report for Sewerage and Water Pollution Control, 1966 February (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] West Sand Lake, Draft Environmental Impact Study for Miller's Supermarket, Inc. Route 43, 1985 August (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Schenectady County, 1948-2008; 4; 6.88 cubic ft.
  This series contains files pertaining to planning decisions in Schenectady County, New York. The majority of the documents involve planning issues within the City of Schenectady, although there are also numerous documents pertaining to the towns of Niskayuna, Glenville, and Rotterdam, as well as several for the Village of Scotia. Of particular note are a series of master/comprehensive plans for the City of Schenectady published in the 1940s, 1970s, and 1990s. This series also contains a variety of sub-area plans for downtown and neighborhood development. Other common file types include: economic analyses (at the municipal and county level), water supply/treatment documents (e.g., aquifer/groundwater and wastewater facilities), housing plans, and recreational facility profiles.
  - [Town of] Duanesburg, Consideration of the Duanesburg Comprehensive Plan [Meeting Notes], 1987 June (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Available Now: Corporations Park [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Comprehensive Master Plan, 1988 December (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Comprehensive Master Plan, 1990 April (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Engineer's Report for Proposed Sewer District No.9, 1997 March (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Glenville Energy Park Project, Project Update #1, 2000 May (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Glenville Town Center Master Plan, Retail Market Overview, 2002 October (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Historical Markers in the Town of Glenville and Village of Scotia, 1995 March (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Land Capability Study: County Farm, Glenridge Hospital, Glendale Home, 1971 August (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Planning and Zoning Commission Meeting Agenda, 2001 April (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Planning Study, 1966 April (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Report on Wastewater Collection and Disposal, 1974 September (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Route 50/Freeman's Bridge Road Corridor Traffic Study, Preliminary Findings, 1993 June (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Subdivision Regulations, 1990 December (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Subdivision Regulations for the Town of Glenville, 1989 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Town Plan, Background Study: Commercial Land Use and Zoning, 1979 January (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - [Town of] Glenville, Zoning Ordinance of the Town of Glenville, 1989 December (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Addition of Secondary Treatment Facilities at the Wastewater Treatment Plant, 1968 June (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Comprehensive Development Plans, 1970-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Engineer's Report, North Trunk Extension Sewer District No.6, Extension No.22, 1974 November (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Environmental Assessment Statement for the Proposed North Trunk Extension Sewer District 6, Extension No.22, 1974 December (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Flood Hazard Area Maps, 1974 March (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Flood Insurance Study, 1976 July (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, A History of Niskayuna, New York Volume 1 [Book], Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Niskayuna Today [Promotional Booklet], 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Niskayuna Transportation Study Group, Study Committee Reports, 1972 May (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Plan-93, Comprehensive Development Plan for the Town of Niskayuna, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Report on Sewerage System Cost Study for Southeast Lisha Kill Area, 1973 April (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Review of the Niskayuna Transportation Study, 1973 January (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Zoning Code, Chapter 220, 1999 March (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - [Town of] Niskayuna, Zoning Map, 1997 August (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - [Town of] Princetown, Final New Sanitation Ordinance, 1973 August (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - [Town of] Princetown, Zoning Law and Land Subdivision Regulation, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Draft Environmental Impact Statement: A New Elementary School Facility, 1989 December (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Draft Environmental Impact Statement: New Elementary School, Schalmont Central School District, 1990 January (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - [Town of], Rotterdam, Wastewater Facility Plan, 1976 January (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, The Master Plan Volume No. 1, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, The Master Plan Volume No. 2, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Northeastern Industrial Park and Rotterdam Industrial Park [Promotional Materials], Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Preliminary Report on Sewerage, 1957 December (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Re: Schenectady Aquifer Wellhead Protection (WHP) Program Demonstration Project, [Memo], 1991 April (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Re: Westview Mall, 1977 June (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Rotterdam Area Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1968 February (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Rotterdam Area Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1968 February (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, The Rotterdam Story: Yesterday, Today and Tomorrow, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Statement Submitted to the Town Board of Rotterdam on Behalf of the City of Schenectady [Re: Aquifer Pollution], 1977 June (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - [Town of] Rotterdam, Survey of Market Potential Westview Mall, 1977 June (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The 400 Block Development, 1980 November (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Application for Urban Beautification and Improvement Grant, 1971 January (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Barney Square Now Leasing [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Better Neighborhoods, Inc. Annual Report, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Broadway Center Project, Draft Environmental Impact Statement, 1987 September (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Broadway Center Project, Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1987 November (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Broadway Center Project, A Supplement to the Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1989 July (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Broadway Center Project, An Amendment to the Final Environmental Impact Statement, 1989 June (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A City in Search of Its Destiny [Newspaper Clippings], 1995 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - [City of] Schenectady, City of Schenectady Historic Resource Survey, Volume 1, 1993 March (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - [City of] Schenectady, City of Schenectady Historic Resource Survey, Volume 2, 1993 March (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - [City of] Schenectady, City of Schenectady, New York, Inventory Report for the Downtown Master Plan, 1999 May (Oversized 2)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Code Enforcement: Does Schenectady Need a System?, 1978 June (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Community Development Team Report [Marked Confidential], 1965 June (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Community Economic Profile [Reference Page], Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Comprehensive City Plan, 1948 September (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Comprehensive Economic Plan, 1983 November (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Comprehensive Plan, 1971 June (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Comprehensive Reorganization Study of the Schenectady School District (1 of 2), 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Comprehensive Reorganization Study of the Schenectady School District (2 of 2), 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Comprehensive Reorganization Study of the Schenectady School District, Appendices, 1988 July (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Development of a Comprehensive Reorganization Plan for the Schenectady School District, 1987 July (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - [City of] Schenectady, "The Dilemmas of Choice: Schenectady 2000" 15th Anniversary Symposium, 1990 June (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Directory of Community Reports, Compiled by Schenectady Bureau of Municipal Research, Inc., 1966-1972 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Downtown Redevelopment Plan, Report of Planning Phase 3, 1975 April (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Downtown Schenectady- An Analysis of Its Economic Potential, 1968 July (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Downtown Schenectady: A New Life/A New Future, Undated (Oversized 2)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Downtown Schenectady, NY, Economic and Market Study, 1979 June (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Downtown Schenectady: Site Reconnaissance, Data Gathering, Analysis and Public Participation [Report], 1999 May (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Factual Guide: City of Schenectady, Department of Planning and Economic Development, 1985 October (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Hamilton Hill NDP, Planning and Design Study, 1971 May (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - [City of] Schenectady, History, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 December (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Housing, 1968 November (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Housing Element, Department of City Development, 1974 December (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Mayor's Task Force on Residential Development as Amended, Final Report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Schenectady County, The Mohawk-Hudson Bike-Hike Trail and Its Impact on Adjoining Residential Properties, 1997 November (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Municipal Ownership of the Electric and Gas Service in Schenectady, A Prefeasibility Study, 1975 August (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Overall Program Design CPA NY-02-36-1061, Department of City Development, 1975 June (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Phase 1 Report, Urban Historic Fabric Map, Building Condition Map, Building Usage Maps, Utility Maps, 1999 May (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Programming Element CPA-NY-02-36-1061, Department of City Development, 1975 June (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Proposal for the Implementation of a Magnet School Program, 1989 March (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Proposal to Provide… Magnet Schools at the Elementary Level, 1990 December (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Recovery Action Plan, Master Plan for Recreation, 1992-1996 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Recreation in Schenectady: Strategies for the Future, Five-Year Recreation Plan, 1982 July (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - [City of] Schenectady, The Return of A City [Promotional Booklet], Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady 2000, Conceptual Design Options, 1993 June (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady and the Arts. [Guide], 1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady Area Educational Resources Foundation for a Growing Community, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady Center: The Capital District's Newest Urban Workplace [Promotional Brochure], Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady Community Survey: Health, Welfare, Recreational Services, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady, New York, Downtown Development Plan, 1970 February (Oversized 2)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Schenectady Urban Cultural Park Management Plan, 1986 January (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Set Your Sites on Schenectady, [Promotional Brochure], 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Social Accounting Report-Schenectady Community, 1981 August (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Social Plan for Schenectady, 1976 July (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - [City of] Schenectady, South Downtown Schenectady Redevelopment Strategy, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Study of Outdoor Recreation Facilities in the City of Schenectady, 1976 June (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - [City of] Schenectady, A Summary of the Mayor's Task Force Report on Housing, 1972 May (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Summit Tower Profile of Residents, 1979 November (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Traffic and Parking Analysis Schenectady Central Business District [Draft], 1969 October (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - [City of] Schenectady, Woodlawn Drainage System, Environmental Impact Assessment, 1979 July (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Schenectady County, Agricultural and Farmland Protection Plan, 2002 September (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Schenectady County, Amendments to the Schenectady Intermunicipal Watershed Rules and Regulations, 1991 April (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County, Application Narrative Community Mental Retardation Centers [Preliminary Draft], 1970 March (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Schenectady County, Appraisal of Potential for Outdoor Recreational Development, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Schenectady County, Audited Financial Statements, Supplementary Information and Single Audit Report, 2008 December (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Schenectady County, Buildable Land, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1969 April (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Schenectady County. Capital District World Trade Center Development Feasibility and Program Recommendations Executive Summary, 1991 May (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Schenectady County, Community Services Directory, Guide to the Human Services of Schenectady County, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Schenectady County, Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study, 1970 March (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Schenectady County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study for Schenectady County, New York, 1970 June (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady County, Comprehensive Sewerage Study, Summary Report, 1970 June (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Schenectady County, Comprehensive Traffic Safety Plan, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady County, Connections: The Monthly Newsletter of the Chamber of Schenectady County, 2002 September (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady County, Critical Human Service Needs in Schenectady County, 1992 October (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady County, Digest of County of Schenectady Comprehensive Sewerage Study, 1969 January (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Schenectady County, Draft Economic Base Study, 1996 November (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady County, Drainage, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 December (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Schenectady County, Early Schenectady County, [History Booklet], Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Schenectady County, Economic Base, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1969 October (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, Economic Profile, 1977 March-1977 June (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Schenectady County: Education, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1968 July (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Schenectady County, The Elderly in Schenectady County, 1976 March (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Schenectady County, Environmental Contacts [Directory], 1979 November (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Schenectady County, Environmental Plan, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Schenectady County, Environmental Plan, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Schenectady County, Environment Plan, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Schenectady County, Environment Plan, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Schenectady County, Feasibility Report Schenectady County Local Correctional Facility, 1979 May (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County, Feasibility Study of the Recreational Potential of the Mohawk Riverfront and Adjacent Islands, 1967 September (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Schenectady County, Final Report on USOE Mini-Grant GOO7903434, Planning, Transportation and Economics, 1980 December (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Schenectady County, Geology, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Schenectady County, The Great Flats Aquifer: A Unique Source of Pure Water in Schenectady County, 1979 March (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Schenectady County, Ground-water Resources of Eastern Schenectady County, New York, With Emphasis on Infiltration from the Mohawk River, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Schenectady County, The Ground-Water Resources of Schenectady County, New York, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Schenectady County, Health Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Schenectady County, Hispanic Studies Program, Final Report, 1989 December (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Schenectady County, History of the Human Services Planning Council of Schenectady County, Inc., 1989 June (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Schenectady County, Homelessness and Health Care in Schenectady County as Seen By Human Service Providers, 1990 May (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Schenectady County, Housing Needs of the Elderly, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Schenectady County, Housing (Part 1), Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Plan, 1967 November (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Schenectady County, Human Services Building Needs Study, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Schenectady County, I Love New York Schenectady County Travel Guide, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Schenectady County, Industrial Development Study of the Schenectady County Airport, the Adjacent Flight Test Center, and the Former Naval Supply Depot, 1967 March (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Schenectady County, Involvement, Schenectady County Chamber of Commerce, Inc., Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Schenectady County, Land Use, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 December (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady County, Land Use and Development Guide, 1978 March-1978 June (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Schenectady County, Libraries, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 October (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady County, Natural Areas of Schenectady County, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady County, Overall Economic Development Plan, 1979 December (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady County, The People of Schenectady County, New York: Trends in Human Resources and Their Characteristics 1900-1960, 1968 August (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Schenectady County, Population, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Plan, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Schenectady County, Profile Schenectady County, 1978 December (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Schenectady County, Profile of Schenectady County, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Schenectady County, A Profile of Schenectady County From 1980 Census Data, 1983 June (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Schenectady County, County Property Tax Guide, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Schenectady County, Public Health Services in Schenectady County, 1988 May (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Schenectady County, Recreation, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, Undated (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Schenectady County, Report on Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study, Preliminary Daft, 1969 May (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Airport Layout Plan [Report], 1970 November (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Aquifer Preservation Study and Report, 1978 August (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Aquifer Preservation Strategy Program, Draft Report, 1980 April (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Aquifer Preservation Strategy Program, Final Report, 1980 August (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Chamber of Commerce, Inc. [Correspondence about Town Government Spending], 1975 November (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, Soils, 1968 March (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Housing Needs Assessment, 1992 October (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Housing Needs Assessment, Review Draft, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady Intermunicipal Watershed Rules and Regulations, [Environmental Impact Statement], 1990 January (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Solid Waste Resource Recovery, Preliminary Feasibility Study, 1984 June (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Solid Waste Resource Recovery, Preliminary Feasibility Study, Executive Summary, 1984 June (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Land Use and Development Guide [Draft Copy], 1977 June (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Schenectady County, Schenectady County Youth Needs Assessment, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Schenectady County, School Districts, Schenectady County Comprehensive Plan: Working Report, 1967 August (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Schenectady County, A Study of Homeless Persons in Schenectady County March-17-May 30, 1986, 1987 March (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Schenectady County, Summary Report: Comprehensive Public Water Supply Study for Schenectady County…, 1970 March (Box 7, Folder 6)